Guide to the William Kent Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- MICROFILM HIST. MSS. 105
  - CHRONOLOGICAL SERIES
    - Clippings from California papers relating to Kent's campaign for election and his victory., 1912 November-December (Box 14)
    - Correspondence between Mr. Kent and various California and national newspaper editors., 1913-1914 (Box 14)
    - Nationwide clippings following Kent's congressional activities and electoral campaign., 1913-1914 (Box 14)
    - Clippings from California papers concerning Kent's congressional activities., 1915-1916 (Box 15)
    - Assorted newspaper clippings on topics ranging from local California affairs to national issues, including the following:, 1897-1951
      - Water issues (Box 15)
      - Temperance (Box 15)
      - Suffrage (Box 15)
      - The Mexican Revolution (Box 15)
      - World War I (Box 15)
      - Kent's 1920 campaign for the Senate (Box 15)
      - War in Ireland (Box 15)
      - Robert LaFollette (Box 15)
      - William Kent's obituary notices (Box 15)
      - Other family death notices (Box 15)
      - Christening of the "William Kent" (Box 15)
      - Mrs. Kent's death (Box 15)